In my last video, I spoke on the
difference between just believing and
actually surrendering. And I used Khloe
as an example because she recently came
out and said that she is a child of God
and that she believes Jesus is the son
of God. Now, a lot of you took issue
with what I said, you know, essentially
saying that I'm just judging her and
that none of us have the right to judge
anybody else's walk with Christ. I
absolutely understand where y'all are
coming from. We as followers of Jesus
Christ, we don't have the right, we
don't have the ability to judge anybody
else's heart. That is God's job and
God's job alone. So what is our job
then? We are to inspect the fruit. We as
followers of Jesus Christ are fruit
inspectors because true saving faith
produces a changed life. True saving
faith produces works. It produces
evidence of that saving faith in your
life. Faith without works is dead. We
are not saved by works. Works cannot
save us. But when we are truly saved,
that salvation produces works. It
produces evidence that others can see,
that others can judge, that others can
tell that we are truly saved. Y'all, we
are called to test the spirits, to have
a discerning spirit, to rightly judge,
to make fair and just evaluations
of fruit. And why are we supposed to do
that? Because if we went by what
everybody says by their lip service,
then we could think that even a Satanist
is a Christian. These people honor me
with their lips, but their hearts are
far from me. See, this is exactly how
deception works. When we just sit back
and say we can't judge and we stop using
discernment, we stop testing the
spirits, we stop inspecting fruit, we
are setting ourselves up to walk right
into the enemy's lies because the enemy
masquerades as an angel of what? Of
light. Now, we'll get to more of her
fruit in a second, but y'all, we are
living in the last days. And now more
than ever, Satan is propping up people
who are pretending to be Christian while
they speak a false and empty gospel
because he wants you to be doing exactly
what a lot of you are already doing
right now. You are sitting back. You are
not using a discerning ear. You are not
inspecting fruit and you are thinking
that what they are saying is evidence of
salvation when it's not. Y'all should at
least be questioning where the mention
is of Jesus being her personal Lord and
Savior. Where's the mention of Jesus
forgiving her sins? Y'all, we need to be
able to discern the enemy's lies and
deceptive practices. Those in this world
with money and fame, top right, if you
missed her, should be a red flag by
themselves, even without all of the
symbolism. This world is ran by Satan,
y'all. You do not get money. You do not
get power. You do not get fame by
sharing the true gospel of the Lord
Jesus Christ. When you start to notice
the symbolism,
it becomes very apparent who these
people are and who they serve. It's
literally all of them if you don't know
already. Should we move on to this
symbolism that I can't say? How about
this one? Or this one? Ah, there it is.
Here's another one. They tell you who
they are. You just have to know what
you're looking for. I can't really say
much about this stuff on here, but uh
take note, especially this one and the
top right one. They're the most common,
y'all. We cannot go just by what people
say. We cannot go just by their lip
service. The Lord tells us that there
are people out in this world who honor
him with their lips, but their hearts
are far from him. We as true followers
of the Lord Jesus Christ cannot be
deceived. We are commanded not to be
deceived. We are commanded to know the
schemes of the enemy, to know how he
moves and how he operates. We are
supposed to test the spirits. We are
supposed to have a discerning ear. We
are supposed to be fruit inspectors.
This doesn't look like fruit of the
spirit to me. There it is again. Even
Satan masquerades as an angel of light,
y'all. And so do his followers. Stop
just listening to what people say, their
lip service. Start looking for fruit. Be
a fruit inspector. Start looking for
evidence in their life of that true
saving faith. Because y'all, the enemy
is hard at work right now to get you
deceived. to get you complacent in your
faith, to get you to stop inspecting
fruit, to get you to think that just
somebody saying, "I believe in God," is
evidence of salvation, when it's not.
This is how deception works, y'all. The
enemy masquerades as an angel of light
and so do his followers.